Yes, so now I am in Ueno!
Yay!
Why am I here in Ueno?
My grandpa used to take me to Ameyoko when I was little.
There was a fancy dagashi shop called Niki's Confectionery, which was a bit bigger than the usual dagashi shop.
My grandfather used to take me there.
I loved it so much that my grandpa and I would buy a lot of dagashi and eat them together.
I've been wanting to go there for a long time, and I haven't been able to go there recently.
I've been wanting to go there for a long time, so I'm happy that I'm going this time.
So I'm on my way to Niki's pastries right now! Yay!
But I also felt a bit lonely shopping by myself, so I wanted to take someone with me.
I've been thinking that I'd like to take someone shopping for sweets.
I'd like to introduce our special guest.
Please join us.
Please invite a very special guest.
I think they're all...
I knew you'd think AmeFlash was...
In one month of AmeFlash, you're Hana Kojima of AmeFlash?
I'm Hana Kojima. Pleased to meet you.
You know how you always wanted to take Hana to Miki's?
Yuzu said I've never been to Miki's.
Yuzu said you'd love it and that she'd love to take you there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah... Sadakashiya has a tiny image, but it's really big.
I've never said that.
Let's buy lots of stuff!
Yay!
So I'd like to buy two machines on loan.
For the time being, of course, it's a prerequisite that I buy one for myself.
And since you and my brother always bought them together, I'd like to buy one for you too.
I want to buy my favorite things for my brother, too.
And also, since I've gone to the trouble of buying the rest of the items...
I also wanted to buy something for the other two members, Ira and Moeka.
I want to buy one for Anna, too.
I'd like to buy one for Ana too.
Can't you and Anna buy it by yourself?
That's true.
Who are you buying it for, Ana?
Well, I'd like to buy one for myself.
I see.
ONLY
Only, only, only.
I won't give it to you.
I wouldn't give it to anyone else.
Since you're here, why don't you go with your dad and...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Only me.
Only
I've got a little extra screen, don't I?
But I hope I can buy it like this.
Well, let's get on with it.
Okay, here we go.
Wait, isn't that Ira?
Wait, is it this big?
Oh, my God, it's huge!
They only have these in a tiny size.
You know, at the convenience store, they always have maple leaf crackers and stuff like that.
Or Momiji senbei crackers.
But Miki's snacks are huge!
Wow!
I found something delicious for Ira right away!
Ira really likes these crackers!
That's Ira, isn't it?
I'll buy them for you.
I'm going to go buy some!
I'll buy you 12,000 yen.
I'll buy these.
Can I buy it?
Let's make it 4,000 yen.
It looks good, but we've already eaten a lot of salty food.
It's time for something sweet.
I like big ones like this.
The majority of our pastries are sold in bulk.
Oh! Speaking of sweets...
But look! Isn't that a lot?
There's so much!
It's amazing!
No one I know has this much.
No, right? I think it's just this one corner, right?
Just a corner.
Wait! May I?
Yes, yes, yes.
Do you want to buy a lot?
I'm buying.
Yeah, I'm buying.
Hey, don't do that doppelganger right there.
Don't do that when you're lucky.
You'll wait for me?
Yes, I will.
See you next time!
Young Donuts has chocolate?
No, they don't.
We buy a lot of them, by the way.
Oh, my God.
What's your budget?
I don't know. I've got three more hours of work to do here.
I can get it.
Let's work.
Okay, I'll work.
Let me work.Please let me work.
Yuuzu, did you and grandpa used to come here often?
Yes, Grandpa.
Every time we came here, Grandpa would bring us.
Do you have any memories of him?
Grandpa didn't really buy anything with us.
He's just happy to bring them here.
I see. He buys a lot of things for his grandchildren.
Yuzu buys a lot of things for him, and he just watches them.
So cute, Grandpa is so cute!
Did he buy something like fruit jelly?
I don't know. Rectangular jelly like this.
The kind that's a little hard.
Grandpa used to buy that every time.
If they had that, I'd definitely buy it.
You have that, don't you?
Where is it?
I'd like to look for it.
Gramps, you're so sweet.
Hey...
Oh, man, local snacks are growing!
Hey!
So many of them.
Smilin', isn't it crazy?
Milk club.
Wow, I want her to try it!
I want to buy it for her.
Isn't that milk?
You said you wanted to do this.
I want to play with milk, too.
But I like this one.
This is for you, too.
Mayaka loves milk.
So I'll buy a milk lab for you.
And one more thing...
I'll buy this for you
I'll buy this for her
Surely this is milk I'm curious about
I want to grab it
I'm looking for a memento of you and grandpa
Let's go upstairs for a look.
It's so big.
It's big, isn't it?
I used to buy this every time.
It's perfect for a gift for a concert.
Oh, yeah! That's a good idea.
But there are so many different flavors.
I think it's a good idea.
My mom loves it when I eat it.
Do you want me to get you a big one?
I'll get you a big one.
Oh, yeah, that's a good idea.
Mom, I'll probably eat it forever.
Oh, it's possible?
I don't see anything yet.
In that case, I'll ask the clerk.
Excuse me, I'm looking for some snacks.
Rectangular, like Jell-O.
Oh, that's it!
It's downstairs!
I'm so happy!
Let's go back downstairs.
I don't see them yet.
Oh, there it is!
There it is! There's a lot of jellies.
This one, this one, this one...
This one!
This one, this one!
I love this!
I would have bought this for sure.
Grandpa.
And I'm buying this one.
Yay!
Gets.
Oh, good, you missed it.
By the way, I'd like to ask you one more thing.
I'd like to ask you about the lyrics of the second season.
I'm curious.
Wow!
Oh!
This is it.
Covered in chocolate!
This, I've had since the day before yesterday, the day before yesterday!
This is the best today!
I've been really indebted to Chocomare lately.
When we go to live shows
When we go to live shows, we bring in snacks and sweets.
I'm sure you have Chocomare, right?
Yes, we do.
They're delicious.
So right now, we have a lot of Mamoru and real chocolates.
And we also have a lot of joual butter.
Oh, my God!
Well, let's see.
During the live performance, everyone's member
So that they get excited.
I'm going to buy some of this chocolate covered and joual butter
I'll buy them as gifts for the show.
Thank you very much.
By the way, Mr. MatsuzawaBy the way, Mr. Matsuzawa
Do you have any recommendations?
Yes, I do.
I have a few right now.
Right now, here it is.
Moonlight cake.
Oh! Moonlight cake?
What? What's that?
You have a Moonlight cake?
So, there's Moonlight.
Black Moon, and a new one.
We're running out of product.
Oh, my God! I knew they were popular.
Would you recommend either of these?
Okay, both of them.
Okay, both.
Okay, let's go.
Okay, I'll bring you some of these, too.
This is amazing.
I've never seen anything like it.
It looks so good!
Food and menu.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
See you soon.
Well, Mr. Watsuwa, you know, there is a famous launch, right?
If you don't mind, we would like to come when we get bigger.
Well, there are only about two.
Oh, really? May we come? You may come.
You may come, Mr. President.
Thank you very much.
Um, yes.
Please.
I'm glad. Thank you very much.
Oh, wow.
This is, thank you very much.
Excuse me.
Thank you very much.
Yay.
I'll be right back. Right away.
Okay.
Well then...
Here!
Here we go.
Yes!
Ta-da!
What do you think?
It's amazing!
Does it look good on me?
It looks great!
Thank you!
Ta-da!
Ta-da lyrics! By the way, there was a big question at the end.
I had so much fun today that I was wondering if you could let me wear this and call out to the audience for a bit.
Is it that light? Is that okay?
Yes!
Is it okay if I advertise in a loud voice from inside the store?
If you say, "Welcome," "Here are some snacks and drinks," or "We have a great deal on all of our products," we'll get a lot of customers.
We have a great deal!
Okay, thank you very much. I will do my best!
I'll do my best!
I knew I'd never done this much before.
I've never had a part-time job before.
It's a little nerve-wracking.
I'm a little nervous.
Well, come on in, senior.
May I?
Welcome! We have Nikinu candy!
We have great deals on everything, so if you see something you like, please buy it!
Welcome! Thank you very much!
We have a great selection, so please buy some!
I'm so glad you like it!
I got a "wow, it's so cute" comment from a customer!
Welcome!
You have a visitor.
Welcome! We do nikinu candy!
Welcome! We have Nikinu candy!
Lots of delicious sweets!
We are waiting for you. Please come and visit us.
Welcome.
Please come in.
Would you like to buy some sweets?
Would you like to buy some sweets? Sweets.
Welcome.
We have a wide variety of sweets.
We hope you enjoy it.
How do I do this for you?
But it's okay, right?
Welcome.
We're doing NIKINOKASHI.
We're doing Niki Nokashi.
We have a lot of good food.
I don't know what to say.
How do I do this for you?
It's difficult, because I don't have the experience yet. I wish I had something to say that would draw you in, but I don't have enough knowledge.It's hard, because I didn't have the experience yet, or more specifically, the good sense to say something that would draw them in, but I also didn't have enough knowledge.
I wish I had something to say that would draw you in, but I also didn't know enough.
I'm glad I had the experience, because I'm going to say, "I've worked with Niki's lyrics before.
I'm proud to say I've done it. I'll help you a little.
I'll help you out a little bit.
All right, let's buy a bunch of stuff!
I bought a lot!
I'm sorry, there were so many!
I bought a lot of stuff.
I've never seen so many of them before... but I was a little kid with rainy skin... and when I was a little girl... I wanted to go back to my childhood... and see more of my childhood.
I was a little kid when I was a little kid, but when I was a little kid, I was a little kid when I was a little kid.
I bought a lot of them and I want to eat them.
How much did you buy?
It was hard to call.
I can only help a little.
It was 4,500 yen.
I was watching the speed of the bill, and it just kept going up and up and up.
I was shaking and I thought, "Oh my God, but I'm so happy to have been able to buy all this stuff.
But it's not just for me, it's for the members and my family too.
I was shaking and thinking, "Oh my God, but I'm so happy!
I figured it's better than 4,500 yen.
By the way, Hana-chan, are you serious? This?
4,700 yen.
I bought it for 200 yen.
It's not a cut or anything.
Myself.
Only for me?
But I want to eat it.
Let's eat it!
I was thinking of eating the mixed fruit jelly that holds memories of my grandfather...
Oh, here it is!
Here, this is the mixed jelly.
I want to eat this!
I miss my grandpa and grandma. I'm sure they were there.
Yes, they did!
Bon appétit!
Is it good?
It brings back memories.
I love it.
It tastes like my grandpa's.
Just like at Grandpa's house.
I miss it so much.
It's just like when I was in elementary school.
This is what you get at Grandpa's house.
I'm so happy! I'm so happy to buy so many side dishes!
I bought a lot for the members, too.
I have to deliver them.
I'll leave them at the show.
I guess so.
Shall we pick them up?
Let's keep it.
For the members.